netsolutionsindia.com 2018-08-19

# Privacy Policy of Net Solutions

This privacy policy has been uniquely compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their 'Personally identifiable information' (PII) is being used online.

PII is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context.

Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

What personal information do we collect from the people that visit our website, blog, landing pages, microsites and newsletter?

#### Information that you provide

When registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter the following information and details to help you with your experience:  
Name  
Email address  
Phone number

This may occur, for example, when you fill an enquiry form or register for a webinar, or download an eBook from our website. Specifically, this happens when you explicitly complete a form on our website to access any type of content.

#### Country data based on your IP

If you register for a webinar or download an eBook, for example, we may collect the location of your device based on your IP address. This helps us delineate where you located in the world, and based on that, we will follow each country's data compliance regulations to their fullest effect.

#### How do we use your information?

We may use the information collected above in the following manner:

  * To personalize your experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product offerings in which you are most interested.
  * To send periodic emails regarding other offers, products and/or services.
  * To send you event-related updates, reminders and confirmations.
  * To send you technical notices, updates, security alerts and support and administrative messages.
  * To respond to your comments, questions and requests and provide customer service and support.
  * To communicate with you about products, services, offers, promotions, rewards and events offered by us, as well as provide news and information we think will be of interest to you.
  * Monitor and analyze trends, usage and activities in connection with our content and website performance.
  * To personalize content and present you with advertising, content or features that we believe will be of interest or useful to you.

#### Email Management

You may receive an email from Net Solutions for a variety of reasons – for example, if you took an action through our website, you signed up for specialty content, or perhaps you registered for an event or conference.

All Net Solutions emails will include a link in the footer, where you can select your communication preferences or unsubscribe altogether.

Also, you can manage your receipt of some types of communication by following the instructions included in the email we send you.

#### When do we share and disclose your information?

Your privacy is extremely important to us and we are committed to protecting your information that identifies you personally. We will only share personal information that you provide us under the following circumstances:

  * With your consent  
When you explicitly consent or allow Net Solutions to share your personal information. This happens when you submit your information through many of our content offers, events or services.  
For example, if you choose to sign up for an exclusive piece of premium content via a form – your name, phone number, email address, job title, and company will be collected by Net Solutions.
  * Legal obligation or protection from harm  
When Net Solutions has a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any requirement of law, regulation, legal process, or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce or investigate a potential violation of the Terms of Use, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise respond to fraud, security or technical concerns, (d) support auditing and compliance functions, or (e) protect the rights, property, or safety of Net Solutions, its users, or the public against harm.
  * Business transfers  
If and when Net Solutions is involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of transfer or sale of some or all of its business, whether as a going concern or as part of the bankruptcy, liquidation, or similar proceeding, we may share your personal information in connection with that transaction.

#### How do we protect visitor information?

Our website is scanned on a regular basis for security breaches and known vulnerabilities in order to make your visit to our site as safe as possible.

We use regular Malware Scanning, as well as an SSL certificate.

#### Third Party Disclosure

When you register for a sponsored event, your information may be shared with our event partners. You may opt out of communications at any time.

#### Third Party Links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

#### Google

Google's advertising requirements can be summed up by Google's Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en>

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website. 

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy. 

We have implemented the following:

  * Remarketing with Google AdSense
  * Demographics and Interests Reporting

We along with third-party vendors, such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions, and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

#### Opting out:

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative opt-out page or permanently using the Google Analytics Opt-out browser add-on.

#### How does our site handle do not track signals?

We honor do not track signals and do not track plant cookies, or use advertising when a Do Not Track (DNT) browser mechanism is in place.

#### COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under 13, the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, the nation's consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children's privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under 13.

#### Fair Information Practices

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

Within 1 Business Day, we will notify the users via email and site notifications

We also agree to the individual redress principle, which requires that individuals have a right to pursue legally enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or a government agency to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

#### CAN-SPAM Act

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to:

  * Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.
  * Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred

To be in accordance with CAN-SPAM we agree to the following:

  * NOT use false, or misleading subjects or email addresses.
  * Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.
  * Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.
  * Monitor third party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.
  * Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.
  * Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

#### Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

15, Rajiv Gandhi Chandigarh Technology Park  
Chandigarh, U.T. 160101  
e-mail: info@netsolutions.com  
Phone: +91 (172) 431-5000
